<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shyam Ramineni</title>
    <link>https://shyamramineni.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Shyam Ramineni</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:30:59 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://shyamramineni.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Java Streams Notes and Examples</title>
      <link>https://shyamramineni.com/posts/java-streams-notes-and-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 19:30:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shyamramineni.com/posts/java-streams-notes-and-examples/</guid>
      <description>Function Interfaces Notes  java.util.functions contains Functional Interfaces which provides target for lambda expressions and method references. method references in Java https://www.baeldung.com/java-method-references default methods in Interface https://www.baeldung.com/java-static-default-methods static methods in Interface https://www.baeldung.com/java-static-default-methods compose functions using andThen like structures - refer to java.util.function.BiFunction functional interface code. Good example https://www.logicbig.com/how-to/code-snippets/jcode-java-functional-interfaces-bifunction-andthen.html  Collections and Stream  Stream operations map, forEach and filter are intermidaite opertions. sort and collect are important functions in streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Website Technical Update 2</title>
      <link>https://shyamramineni.com/posts/personal-website-technical-update-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Mar 2018 17:02:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shyamramineni.com/posts/personal-website-technical-update-2/</guid>
      <description>This is an update on the technical stack of my website. I was able to get Hugo site hosted on S3 based website hosting. I then setup CloudFront based distribution with S3 bucket as Origin. I used CloudFront, not for performance reasons, but to enable HTTPS support. I created custom SSL certification using ACM and set up my custom domain to point to CloudFront distribution using Route53. I set up the whole process as CodeBuild script.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Website Technical - Update 1</title>
      <link>https://shyamramineni.com/posts/personal-website-technical-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 19:30:59 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shyamramineni.com/posts/personal-website-technical-update/</guid>
      <description> Today I was able to get this website up and running based on GitHub based workflow. I commit content markdown into GitHub, then I manually fire AWS codebuild. Build then picks up the source code of hugo project, runs Hugo, updates S3 bucket with static HTML.
Things TODO  Automate build based GitHub pull request Figure out images Organize content by Tags and Categories Create pages  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Website using Hugo, AWS S3</title>
      <link>https://shyamramineni.com/posts/hugo-aws-s3-personal-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 15:44:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://shyamramineni.com/posts/hugo-aws-s3-personal-website/</guid>
      <description>This is first post on my personal website which I developed using Hugo. This site hosted on AWS using S3 static web hosting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>